https://neseal.com/terms/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy - neseal.com
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which NE Seal collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the neseal.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by NE Seal.
Non-Personal Identification Information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
NE Seal has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
NE Seal
neseal.com
anyseal ATgmail DOTCOM
